thecube.com 2019-06-09

# Privacy Policy

The NFHS Network is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy explains our policy regarding the collection, use, disclosure and transfer of your information. This policy may change from time to time, so please refer back to it periodically. By accessing our website or otherwise using our service, you consent to our information practices.

We receive and store information, including personal information, about you and your use of our service. This information is gathered in a number of ways, including when you enter it on our website and from interactions with our service. Personal information is information that can be used to uniquely identify or contact you. Non-personal information is information that does not permit direct association with you. We may collect, use, transfer and disclose non-personal information for any purpose. You can choose not to provide personal information we may request of you, but, in general, most of the personal information we request is required in order to provide our service and the lack of such personal information will prevent us from doing so.

## Collection and Use of Information

When you interact with us, we may ask you to supply us with personal information so that we can provide, enhance and personalize our services and marketing efforts. For similar reasons, we may supplement the personal information you provide with publicly available information about you as well as information from other sources, as permitted by law.

The information we may collect from you directly includes:

  1. Contact information, such as name, email address, postal address, phone number, and mobile number.
  2. User name, which is your email address, and password.
  3. Age and date of birth.
  4. Other demographic information, such as gender, job information, and zip code.
  5. Your preferences, such as favorite schools or preferred channels on our site and other user interfaces.
  6. Communications preferences, such as which newsletters you would like to receive.
  7. Search queries.
  8. In limited circumstances, payment and identity verification information, such as credit card number.
  9. Contact information about others when you provide information about others or refer a friend to a particular site or service (note: such information is used solely to facilitate the communications requested).
  10. Correspondence you send to us.

Information we may collect automatically on our site and other user interfaces:

  1. Your browser type and operating system.
  2. Your Internet Protocol (IP) address, which is the number automatically assigned to your computer whenever you access the Internet and that can sometimes be used to derive your general geographic area.
  3. Sites you visited before and after visiting our site.
  4. Web pages and advertisements you view and links you click on.
  5. Unique identifiers, including mobile device identification numbers that can identify the physical location of such devices in accordance with applicable law.
  6. Information collected through cookies, web beacons, and other technologies.
  7. Information about your interactions with audio and video content, such as the type of content listened to and viewed, and information about your interactions with email messages, such as the links clicked on and whether the messages were opened or forwarded.
  8. Upon request, your bandwidth speed and information about the software programs installed on your computer.
  9. Standard server log information.

## Newsletters and Promotional Emails

We may use your e-mail address or other methods to send you newsletters, as well as messages about new website features, special offers, promotional announcements, consumer surveys and other correspondence concerning our service. If you no longer want to receive marketing promotions from us, simply use your account name and password to access your account information on our website and uncheck those items to unsubscribe or click on the unsubscribe link in our email communications. Please note that you cannot unsubscribe from certain correspondence from us, including messages relating to your account transactions.

## NFHS Network Rewards

The NFHS Rewards program connects NFHS subscribers with third party providers offering certain products or services. The NFHS Network is not responsible for products or services purchased or obtained through the NFHS Network Rewards program and does not make any guarantee, warranty, or representation of any kind regarding products or services purchased through the NFHS Network Rewards program, including but not limited to, warranties of merchantability or fitness for a particular purpose.  The NFHS Network does not endorse any provider of goods or services through the NFHS Network Rewards program.  You may be subject to additional terms and conditions, warranties, or other requirements of the merchant, manufacturer, or other provider of Rewards. You release and hold NFHS Network, and all parties associated with the NFHS Network Rewards Program harmless from any claim, liability, or damage relating to the Program or your use of NFHS Network Rewards program products or services.

## Disclosure of Information

The NFHS Network is committed to maintaining your trust and we want you to understand when and with whom we may share information collected about you.

### With your consent

With your consent, we may share your contact information with third-party business partners.

### Authorized third-party service providers

We share your information with third-party vendors who help us with specialized services, including customer support, email and text message deployment, business analytics, marketing, and data processing. These third parties are allowed to use your information to help us provide our services and not for any other purpose.

### Co-Branded Partners

Co-Branded Partners are third parties with whom we may jointly offer a service or feature. You can tell when you are accessing a service offered by a Co-Branded Partner because the Co-Branded Partner's name will be featured prominently. You may be asked to provide information about yourself to register for a service offered by a Co-Branded Partner. In doing so, you may be providing your information to both us and the Co-Branded Partner, or we may share your information with the Co-Branded Partner. Please note that the Co-Branded Partner's privacy policy may apply to its use of your information.

### Business transfers

We may share your information in connection with a substantial corporate transaction, such as the sale of an NFHS Network website or application, a merger, consolidation, asset sale, or in the unlikely event of bankruptcy.

### Legal requirements

We may disclose information about our users, including contact information, to respond to subpoenas, court orders, legal process, and other law enforcement measures, and to comply with other legal obligations, such as FCC requirements.

### Protect our websites and users

We may disclose information to protect and defend the legal rights, interests, and safety of NFHS Network, our employees, agents, and contractors (including enforcing our agreements); to protect the safety and security of users our website and members of the public; and as otherwise disclosed in our terms of use.

Please note that we may share information with advertisers. We also may share aggregated or anonymized information with third parties, including to help us develop content and services we hope you will find of interest or to help these third parties develop their own products and service offerings. This sharing of anonymized or aggregated information will not include information that could be used to individually identify you.

## Social Sharing

You may elect to share information about your use of the theNFHS Network service, including what you watch, within the NFHS Network as well as on other social networks.

## Access

If you choose to share contact information with us, you may have the opportunity to update that information on our website. You also may update or amend your information by contacting us. If you ask us to deactivate your account, we will disable your account within a reasonable period of time. Please note that we may need to retain some information about you in order to satisfy our legal and security obligations. For example, some of your information may remain in back-up storage even if you ask us to delete it. In some cases, you may be entitled under local laws to access or object to the processing of information that we hold relating to you.

## Children

You must be 13 years of age or older to subscribe to the NFHS Network service. In certain jurisdictions, the age of majority may be older than 18, in which case, you must satisfy that age in order to become a member. While individuals under the age of 18 may utilize the service, they may do so only with the involvement, supervision, and approval of a parent or legal guardian, and subject to our Terms of Use.

## Cookies and Other Technologies

As you interact with our service, we and our service providers may place cookies on your system. Cookies are small pieces of data that are sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your system for record keeping purposes. In general, cookies can make the Internet more useful by storing information about your preferences on a particular system.

In addition to cookies, we and our service providers use a variety of other technologies, including pixel tags (web beacons), clear gifs, or other technologies built into our application software, to gather information on how you interact with our service. These cookies and other technologies can help personalize the service for you and help associate your interactions with our service to other information within your account. They can show us, for example, popular pages, conversion rates, viewing patterns, click-through and other information that can be used to improve, operate and monitor our website and other aspects of our service.

The Help portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. If your browser is set to not accept any cookies, you will not be able to use the NFHS Network service or website.

## Remarketing

​This website uses the Google AdWords remarketing service to advertise on third party websites (including Google) to previous visitors to our site. It could mean that we advertise to previous visitors who haven’t completed a task on our site, such as registering to become a member. This could be in the form of an advertisement on the Google search results page, or a site in the Google Display Network. Third-party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on someone’s past visits to our website. Of course, any data collected will be used in accordance with our own privacy policy and Google’s privacy policy.  You can set your preferences for how Google advertises to you using the [Google Ad Preferences page](https://www.google.com/settings/u/0/ads/authenticated), and if you want to you can [opt out of interest-based advertising entirely by cookie settings](https://www.google.com/settings/u/0/ads/authenticated) or opt out of a third-party vendor's use of cookies by visiting the [Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/).

## Third Party Advertisers

We permit CBS Interactive Inc. and its affiliates, partners, and advertisers (“third-party advertisers”) to place tags, scripts, and beacons (“third-party tags”) on our site as part of the advertisements displayed on our sites. These third-party tags may set cookies on your device and may also gather information about your device and the pages you visit on our site and on other sites that display third-party tags. Our third-party advertisers use the information gathered through third-party tags in accordance with their respective privacy policies. CBS Interactive Inc.’s privacy policy is available athttps://www.cbsinteractive.com/legal/cbsi/privacy-policy. By visiting our sites, you consent to the automatic collection and use of information by our third party advertisers in accordance with this policy and with the third party advertisers’ privacy policies as posted from time to time.

If streaming videos displayed on our sites include third-party tags, the third parties that have provided the third-party tags may also receive information about videos you watch on our sites, and you consent to the sharing of this information.

## Security of Information

The NFHS Network takes information security very seriously and uses reasonable administrative, technical, physical and managerial measures to protect your personal information from unauthorized access. Unfortunately, no security system can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Accordingly, we cannot guarantee the security of your information and cannot assume liability for improper access to it. By using our service, including our website and user interfaces, or providing information to us through any means, you agree that we can communicate with you electronically regarding security, privacy, and administrative issues relating to your use of the NFHS Network service. You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your account access information and for restricting access to your computer or device through which you access your NFHS Network account. If you disclose your password to anyone or share your account and/or devices with other people, you take full responsibility for their actions. Where possible, users of public or shared devices should log out at the completion of each visit. If you sell or return a computer or device, you should log-out and deactivate the device before doing so. If you fail to log out and deactivate your device, subsequent users may be able to access your account information.

## Contacting Us

If you have questions concerning your account or this Privacy Policy, including the treatment of your personal information and/or our use of cookies and other technologies, please contact us via email at [memberadmin@nfhsnetwork.com](mailto:memberadmin@nfhsnetwork.com?subject=Privacy%20Policy%20Question), or at the following:

**The NFHS Network, LLC**  
2835 Brandywine Road #102  
Atlanta, Georgia 30341  
Attn: Legal Department

Updated: September 18, 2018
